bumblebee what do you mean tough guy
betrayed us we do not yet have
definitive proof but it's not looking
good
don't worry though [ __ ] I will protect
you if the time calls for it of course
bumblebee I trust you with my life
good now let's go we don't know when
robot man and his robot boys will arrive
Satan what is it robot man I know where
he will strike next
spit it out [ __ ] we don't have much
time you're crazy if you think you are
getting away with this robot man I'm
sorry to say boy I already a.m.
you see one of your friends or should I
say ex friends have already come to my
side [ __ ]
none of my friends would ever join your
smelly butt maybe you would rather
listen to him
no tough guy what are you doing why did
you join robot man listen here [ __ ] in
this world only the strong will rule
I'm through standing by like a weak ass
[ __ ]
starting this day you will treat me like
a God or you will die it's as simple as
that [ __ ] a [ __ ] just try me
I [ __ ] dare you I've had enough of
your pathetic words robot boys kill him
kill him right now I command you